{
    "id": "976c608943374d1b88f55726923125df",
    "title": "Can, could, may, might",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "71719af2912c422daf9834dbfd420b15",
            "title": "Can, Could, May, Might",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I ……………….. swim across the river.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Can",
                        "May",
                        "Might"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………….. you lift this box?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Can",
                        "May",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………. I come in?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Can",
                        "May",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… I borrow your bicycle?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Can",
                        "May",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It ………………… rain in the evening.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may",
                        "can",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. this be true?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Can",
                        "May",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It ………………… not be true.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "cannot",
                        "may not",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………….. you find love and happiness!",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Can",
                        "May",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………. swim across the river when I was young.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "could",
                        "might",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She said that she ……………… come.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "may",
                        "might",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}